Location Tel Aviv, Israel

Phone <u>058-7316799</u>

Email or@druker.net

WWW druker.net

LinkedIn linkedin.com/in/or-druker

Motivated self-taught technologist with 2+ years of hands-on experience in R&D. Demonstrated talent for adversarial thinking, bug hunting, and writing test plans. Professional knowledge of modern JavaScript frameworks with attention to detail. Seeking a position as a QA Engineer, where I can help maintain a well-tested and stable apps.

Work History

Founder (Freelance)

03/2022 - Current

Druker Dev - Freelance, Remote

- Deployed and tested a system of 7 cross-browser optimized templates on top of React, Next.js, and Tailwind CSS to sell well-designed websites to small business owners and freelancers.
- Recommended refactoring changes to website architecture, content, and linking to improve SEO positions for target keywords and overall user experience based on manual tests and AI systems.

Full Stack Developer (Freelance)

08/2020 - Current

Druker Net - Freelance. Remote

- · Developed and tested <u>full stack web app projects</u>, based on the emerging trends in web and mobile technologies, asynchronous programming, responsive design, and UI/UX best practices.
- Resolved technical problems of 15 developers in the dev community by reviewing their code.

Customer Success Representative

07/2019 - 03/2022

Hemlock Printers, Burnaby, BC (Canada)

- Developed 3 automated end-to-end tests using Selenium and Puppeteer to improve the engineering team productivity, billing process, and customer satisfaction with innovative IT initiatives.
- Managed risk-benefits analysis to make purchasing decisions and successful B2B negotiation of long-term contract renewals with customers to improve revenue by 7.5% per year.
- Provided customer support to over 50 internal and external customers of the company's top 10% profitable accounts (enterprise clients), including product demos and technical assistance.

Prepress Operator

06/2018 - 04/2019

Hemlock Printers, Burnaby, BC (Canada)

• Utilized Adobe InDesign, Illustrator and PhotoShop to prepare and test jobs for color proofs and print.

Skills

Autodidacticism

Studied web and mobile app technologies by relying on online resources, documentation, coding mentors, computer science lectures, and dev communities, including HTTP, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, React JS, React Native, Databases (SQL & NoSQL), Redis, Caching, Node.is, Java, Python.

Interpersonal Skills

Demonstrated creativity, innovation, leadership, analytical thinking, enthusiasm, passion, systems thinking, and critical thinking to collaborate positively with my colleagues.

Data Analysis

Served 4 years in a highly competitive role in **Unit 8200** while working as a **Traffic Analyst** in the equivalent of a fast-paced startup environment. Promoted to be a **Course Instructor** and received an honor badge.

Education

Diploma: Graphic Communications Technology Management

09/2017 - 06/2018

British Columbia Institute of Technology | Burnaby, BC, Canada

10/2012 - 06/2017

Bachelor of Arts: Psychology & Comparative Literature The Hebrew University of Jerusalem | Jerusalem, Israel